<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE rfc [
  <!ENTITY nbsp    "&#160;">
  <!ENTITY zwsp   "&#8203;">
  <!ENTITY nbhy   "&#8209;">
  <!ENTITY wj     "&#8288;">
]>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='rfc2629.xslt' ?>
<rfc xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
     ipr="trust200902"
     docName="draft-farley-acta-knowledge-units-00"
     category="info"
     submissionType="independent"
     tocInclude="true"
     sortRefs="true"
     symRefs="true"
     version="3">

  <front>
    <title abbrev="Knowledge Units">Knowledge Units for Multi-Model Deliberation</title>

    <seriesInfo name="Internet-Draft" value="draft-farley-acta-knowledge-units-00"/>

    <author fullname="Tom Farley" initials="T." surname="Farley">
      <organization>Veritas Acta</organization>
      <address>
        <email>tjf@veritasacta.com</email>
        <uri>https://veritasacta.com</uri>
      </address>
    </author>

    <date year="2026" month="April" day="6"/>

    <area>General</area>
    <workgroup>Network Working Group</workgroup>

    <keyword>knowledge-unit</keyword>
    <keyword>multi-model</keyword>
    <keyword>deliberation</keyword>
    <keyword>consensus</keyword>
    <keyword>signed-receipts</keyword>
    <keyword>Ed25519</keyword>

    <abstract>
      <t>This document defines the Knowledge Unit (KU) format for
      representing verified knowledge produced through structured
      multi-model deliberation.  A Knowledge Unit captures the question
      asked, the models that participated, the consensus achieved, the
      points of agreement and disagreement, and the cryptographic
      receipts that bind each deliberation round to an independently
      verifiable chain.</t>

      <t>The format addresses the epistemic integrity gap in
      LLM-maintained knowledge bases: how to prove that knowledge was
      derived through a rigorous process, that disagreement was preserved
      rather than smoothed away, and that the record has not been
      tampered with.</t>

      <t>This specification complements draft-farley-acta-signed-receipts,
      which defines the receipt format and verification protocol used to
      sign individual deliberation rounds.</t>
    </abstract>
  </front>

  <middle>
    <section anchor="introduction" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Introduction</name>

      <t>Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly used to produce,
      curate, and maintain knowledge bases.  The "LLM Wiki" pattern,
      in which an LLM incrementally compiles and maintains a structured
      collection of interlinked documents from raw sources, has gained
      significant adoption.  Multiple independent implementations have
      appeared across personal research, team knowledge management,
      and agent memory systems.</t>

      <t>While effective for content maintenance, single-model knowledge
      bases lack three properties critical for shared knowledge:</t>

      <ol>
        <li>Multi-perspective verification: A single model's output
        reflects its training data biases and architectural limitations.
        Multiple models with different training corpora and architectures
        provide independent perspectives that surface blind spots no
        single model can detect.</li>

        <li>Structured disagreement: When models disagree, the
        disagreement itself is informative.  Current approaches either
        smooth away disagreement through editorial synthesis or fail to
        capture it structurally.  Readers see false certainty rather than
        the actual state of knowledge.</li>

        <li>Cryptographic provenance: Mutable logs and git histories can
        be rewritten.  Content hashes prove freshness but not
        authenticity.  Tamper-evident provenance requires cryptographic
        signatures bound to each deliberation step, independently
        verifiable by any party without trusting the knowledge base
        operator.</li>
      </ol>

      <t>This document defines the Knowledge Unit (KU) format to address
      these gaps.  A KU is the output of a structured multi-model
      deliberation process in which:</t>

      <ul>
        <li>Multiple frontier models independently answer a question
        (Round 1)</li>
        <li>Models critique each other's responses in assigned adversarial
        roles (Round 2)</li>
        <li>A synthesis engine extracts agreement and disagreement
        (Round 3)</li>
        <li>Every round response is Ed25519-signed per
        <xref target="I-D.farley-acta-signed-receipts"/></li>
      </ul>

      <t>The result is a self-contained knowledge artifact that records
      WHAT is known, HOW it was determined, WHERE models agree and
      disagree, and provides CRYPTOGRAPHIC PROOF of the entire
      process.</t>

      <t>A Knowledge Unit is not a replacement for single-model wikis.
      It is the artifact produced when a question is important enough
      to warrant multi-model deliberation with cryptographic proof.
      Many wiki entries do not need this level of rigour.  KUs are
      for the entries that do.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="conventions" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Conventions and Definitions</name>

      <t>The key words "MUST", "MUST NOT", "REQUIRED", "SHALL", "SHALL
      NOT", "SHOULD", "SHOULD NOT", "RECOMMENDED", "NOT RECOMMENDED",
      "MAY", and "OPTIONAL" in this document are to be interpreted as
      described in BCP 14 <xref target="RFC2119"/> <xref target="RFC8174"/>
      when, and only when, they appear in all capitals, as shown
      here.</t>

      <dl>
        <dt>KU:</dt>
        <dd>Knowledge Unit.  The atomic unit of verified knowledge
        produced through multi-model deliberation.</dd>

        <dt>Deliberation:</dt>
        <dd>A structured multi-round process in which multiple models
        produce, critique, and synthesise responses to a question.</dd>

        <dt>Receipt:</dt>
        <dd>An Ed25519-signed artifact attesting to a specific
        deliberation round, as defined in
        <xref target="I-D.farley-acta-signed-receipts"/>.</dd>

        <dt>Consensus Level:</dt>
        <dd>A structural classification of agreement among participating
        models, determined mechanically from the deliberation
        output.</dd>

        <dt>Roster:</dt>
        <dd>The set of models participating in a deliberation, along
        with their versions and identifiers.</dd>

        <dt>Source:</dt>
        <dd>An input document, article, dataset, or other artifact that
        provides context for the deliberation.  Sources are immutable
        once ingested.</dd>

        <dt>Volatility:</dt>
        <dd>The expected rate of change for the knowledge domain a KU
        covers, which informs freshness intervals.</dd>
      </dl>
    </section>

    <section anchor="schema" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Knowledge Unit Schema</name>

      <t>A Knowledge Unit MUST be represented as a JSON object conforming
      to the schema defined in this section.  Implementations MUST
      support JSON serialisation.  Implementations MAY support additional
      serialisation formats (e.g., CBOR, YAML frontmatter).  See
      <xref target="alt-serialization"/> for alternative serialisation
      guidance.</t>

      <section anchor="core-fields" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Core Fields</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>id (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>Unique identifier for this Knowledge Unit.  The format
          MUST be "ku-" followed by a 12-character alphanumeric string
          (e.g., "ku-z36vuoreb2k3").  The identifier MUST be immutable
          once assigned.  Implementations MUST NOT reuse
          identifiers.</dd>

          <dt>version (integer, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>Schema version number.  The current version is 1.
          Implementations MUST reject KUs with unrecognised version
          numbers.</dd>

          <dt>canonical_question (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>The definitive question this KU answers.  See
          <xref target="canonical-question"/> for canonicalization rules.
          This field MUST NOT be empty.</dd>

          <dt>domain (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Topic classification.  Recommended values include
          "technology", "science", "health", "policy", "economics",
          "agent_security", "agent_governance", "research",
          "engineering".  Implementations SHOULD use values from this
          list where applicable but MAY define additional domain
          values.</dd>

          <dt>tags (array of strings, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Additional classification labels for cross-domain
          discovery.  Implementations SHOULD use lowercase,
          hyphen-separated values (e.g., "machine-learning",
          "climate-policy").</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="consensus-fields" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Consensus Fields</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>consensus_level (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>The level of agreement among participating models.  MUST be
          one of: "unanimous", "strong", "split", "divergent".  See
          <xref target="consensus-levels"/> for definitions.</dd>

          <dt>agreed (array, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd><t>Points where all participating models converge.  Each
          element MUST be either a string containing a claim text, or an
          object with the fields: claim (string, REQUIRED), confidence
          (string, OPTIONAL: "high"/"medium"/"low"), evidence (string,
          OPTIONAL), source_refs (array of strings, OPTIONAL: references
          to source identifiers from the sources array).</t>
          <t>The array MUST NOT be empty for KUs with consensus_level
          "unanimous" or "strong".</t></dd>

          <dt>disputed (array, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Points where models diverge.  Each element MUST be an
          object with: claim (string, REQUIRED), positions (object,
          REQUIRED: map from model identifier to position), significance
          (string, OPTIONAL: "core", "framing", or "edge_case").</dd>

          <dt>uncertain (array, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Points that no model could resolve with confidence.  Each
          element MUST be either a string or an object with: claim
          (string, REQUIRED), reason (string, OPTIONAL: e.g.,
          "insufficient evidence", "outside training data", "rapidly
          evolving area").</dd>

          <dt>synthesis (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>A human-readable summary paragraph produced by the
          synthesis engine (Round 3).  IMPORTANT: The synthesis field is
          NOT part of the canonical knowledge record.  It is an editorial
          convenience produced by a single model and may introduce
          editorial bias.  Implementations MUST NOT treat the synthesis
          as authoritative.  The authoritative content is the agreed,
          disputed, and uncertain arrays.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="provenance-fields" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Provenance Fields</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>models_used (array of strings, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>Model identifiers used in this deliberation.  Each
          identifier SHOULD follow a provider/model format (e.g.,
          "anthropic/claude-opus-4", "openai/gpt-5").</dd>

          <dt>roster_version (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>ISO 8601 date of the model roster snapshot used for this
          deliberation.</dd>

          <dt>roster_hash (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>SHA-256 hash of the sorted models_used array, encoded as
          lowercase hexadecimal.</dd>

          <dt>process_template (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>The deliberation process template used.  Default value:
          "3-round".  Implementations MUST document any non-default
          process templates.</dd>

          <dt>total_tokens (integer, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Total tokens consumed across all rounds and models.</dd>

          <dt>total_cost_cents (number, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Total API cost in US cents for the deliberation.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="source-provenance" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Source Provenance</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>sources (array, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd><t>Source documents that provided context for the
          deliberation.  Each element MUST be an object with: uri
          (string, REQUIRED), title (string, OPTIONAL), content_hash
          (string, REQUIRED: SHA-256 with "sha256:" prefix), ingested_at
          (string, REQUIRED: ISO 8601).</t>
          <t>When a source's content changes (its hash no longer matches
          the stored content_hash), any KU derived from that source
          SHOULD be considered potentially stale, regardless of its
          fresh_until value.</t></dd>

          <dt>source_url (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>URL of the primary source.  Retained for backwards
          compatibility; new implementations SHOULD use the sources
          array.</dd>

          <dt>source_title (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Title of the primary source document.  Retained for
          backwards compatibility.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="lifecycle-fields" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Lifecycle Fields</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>status (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>Current lifecycle state.  MUST be one of: "active",
          "stale", "superseded".  See
          <xref target="lifecycle"/>.</dd>

          <dt>fresh_until (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>ISO 8601 datetime after which this KU SHOULD be considered
          potentially stale.  Default intervals by volatility: "stable"
          365 days, "evolving" 90 days (default), "volatile" 30
          days.</dd>

          <dt>volatility (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>Expected rate of change for this knowledge domain.  MUST
          be one of: "stable" (unlikely to change, e.g., established
          science), "evolving" (changes over months, e.g., best
          practices; default), "volatile" (changes over weeks, e.g.,
          benchmark rankings).</dd>

          <dt>supersedes (string or null, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>The id of the KU this KU replaces.</dd>

          <dt>parent_ku_id (string or null, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>The id of a parent KU from which this KU's question was
          derived.</dd>

          <dt>published_at (string, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd>ISO 8601 datetime of publication.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="receipt-fields" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Receipt Fields</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>receipt_sig (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>The aggregate Ed25519 signature over the receipt chain
          hash, encoded as lowercase hexadecimal.</dd>

          <dt>receipt_kid (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>Key identifier for the signing key.</dd>

          <dt>receipt_hash (string, REQUIRED):</dt>
          <dd>SHA-256 hash of the chained per-round receipt hashes.
          See <xref target="receipt-binding"/>.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="relations" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Inter-KU Relations</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>relations (array, OPTIONAL):</dt>
          <dd><t>Typed relations to other Knowledge Units.  Each element
          MUST be an object with: target_ku_id (string, REQUIRED),
          relation (string, REQUIRED: one of "supports", "contradicts",
          "refines", "extends", "depends_on"), claims (array of strings,
          OPTIONAL: specific claims the relation applies to).</t>
          <t>Relations are directional.  Implementations SHOULD maintain
          bidirectional awareness by adding reciprocal relations when
          discovered.</t></dd>
        </dl>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section anchor="deliberation" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Deliberation Process</name>

      <t>The default deliberation process ("3-round") consists of three
      rounds.  Implementations MAY define additional process templates;
      the process_template field MUST indicate which was used.</t>

      <section anchor="round1" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Round 1: Independent</name>

        <t>Each participating model independently answers the canonical
        question.  Models MUST NOT be shown each other's responses during
        Round 1.  Implementations SHOULD present responses to subsequent
        rounds using blind labels (e.g., "Response A", "Response B") to
        prevent anchoring on perceived model authority.</t>

        <t>Implementations SHOULD include at least one model from a
        different training lineage than the majority (e.g., at least one
        non-US model when the majority are US-trained).</t>

        <t>Each Round 1 response MUST be signed per
        <xref target="I-D.farley-acta-signed-receipts"/>.</t>

        <t>The response record MUST include: ku_id, round (1), slot
        (1-based), model identifier, role ("independent"), content,
        content_hash (SHA-256), receipt_sig (Ed25519), and
        receipt_kid.</t>
      </section>

      <section anchor="round2" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Round 2: Adversarial Critique</name>

        <t>Models are presented with all Round 1 responses (using blind
        labels) and assigned critique roles.  Recommended roles include:
        verifier (checks factual claims), devil_advocate (argues against
        the emerging consensus), synthesizer (identifies common ground),
        clarity_editor (ensures responses are unambiguous).</t>

        <t>Implementations SHOULD assign different roles to different
        models.  At least one model MUST be assigned a role that
        challenges the emerging consensus.  Each Round 2 response MUST
        be signed.</t>
      </section>

      <section anchor="round3" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Round 3: Synthesis</name>

        <t>A synthesis engine processes all Round 1 and Round 2 responses
        to produce: agreed (array), disputed (array), uncertain (array),
        consensus_level (string), and follow_ups (array, OPTIONAL).</t>

        <t>The synthesis output MUST be signed.  The synthesis engine
        MUST NOT invent claims that do not appear in Round 1 or Round 2
        responses.  Its role is extraction and classification, not
        generation.</t>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section anchor="consensus-levels" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Consensus Levels</name>

      <t>Consensus levels are determined structurally by the synthesis
      engine based on agreement patterns.  Consensus levels MUST NOT be
      assigned editorially.</t>

      <dl>
        <dt>unanimous:</dt>
        <dd>All models converge on the same core claims.  The disputed
        array MUST be empty.</dd>

        <dt>strong:</dt>
        <dd>Models agree on the core answer but differ on emphasis or
        edge cases.  The disputed array MAY contain minor points.</dd>

        <dt>split:</dt>
        <dd>Models agree on some claims but diverge substantively on at
        least one core claim.  The disputed array MUST contain at least
        one entry with significance "core".</dd>

        <dt>divergent:</dt>
        <dd>No meaningful common ground.  Models reach fundamentally
        different conclusions.</dd>
      </dl>

      <t>IMPORTANT: Consensus among AI models is evidence, not proof.
      Strong consensus means multiple models with different training
      data, architectures, and potential biases independently arrived at
      similar conclusions.  It does not establish truth.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="canonical-question" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Canonical Question Resolution</name>

      <t>Different phrasings of the same question SHOULD resolve to the
      same canonical_question.  Canonicalization serves three purposes:
      deduplication, linking (hierarchical knowledge structures), and
      discovery.</t>

      <t>The canonicalization model is hierarchical inheritance: a
      general question serves as the canonical anchor, and specific
      variants (audience, constraint, temporal) inherit from it and add
      specialized components.  Each variant MAY produce its own KU with
      a parent_ku_id reference.</t>

      <t>Implementations MUST normalise questions by: converting to
      lowercase, removing leading/trailing whitespace, removing trailing
      punctuation, reducing consecutive whitespace, and removing filler
      phrases.  Implementations SHOULD additionally apply domain-specific
      synonym resolution and normalise named entities to canonical
      forms.</t>

      <t>Before initiating a new deliberation, implementations SHOULD
      check whether a KU already exists for the normalised canonical
      question.  If an active KU exists, the implementation SHOULD
      return it rather than re-deliberating, unless the KU is stale or
      fresh deliberation is explicitly requested.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="lifecycle" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Lifecycle Management</name>

      <section anchor="states" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>States</name>

        <dl>
          <dt>active:</dt>
          <dd>Produced within its freshness window, not superseded.</dd>

          <dt>stale:</dt>
          <dd>Current time exceeds fresh_until, or a source content_hash
          no longer matches.  SHOULD be re-deliberated.</dd>

          <dt>superseded:</dt>
          <dd>A newer KU with supersedes pointing to this KU exists.
          MUST NOT be modified.  Receipts remain verifiable.</dd>
        </dl>
      </section>

      <section anchor="operations" numbered="true" toc="default">
        <name>Operations</name>

        <t>KEEP: Re-deliberation confirms same conclusions; fresh_until
        extended.  UPDATE: Refines without contradiction; new KU with
        supersedes link.  SUPERSEDE: Contradicts previous consensus;
        same mechanics as UPDATE.  MERGE: Overlapping KUs combined into
        one.  ARCHIVE: No longer relevant; superseded with no
        replacement.</t>

        <t>IMPORTANT: Published KUs are NEVER modified in place.  All
        changes produce new KUs with supersedes links.</t>
      </section>
    </section>

    <section anchor="receipt-binding" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Receipt Binding</name>

      <t>For a standard 3-round deliberation with N models, the
      receipt_hash is computed as:</t>

      <artwork><![CDATA[
round1_hash = SHA-256(r1_1.sig || r1_2.sig || ... || r1_N.sig)
round2_hash = SHA-256(r2_1.sig || r2_2.sig || ... || r2_N.sig)
round3_hash = SHA-256(r3_synth.sig)
receipt_hash = SHA-256(round1_hash || round2_hash || round3_hash)
      ]]></artwork>

      <t>The receipt_sig is produced by signing receipt_hash with the
      gateway's Ed25519 private key per <xref target="RFC8032"/>.
      Verification uses Ed25519-Verify(public_key, receipt_hash,
      receipt_sig).  The public key MUST be retrievable through the
      receipt_kid field or direct inclusion.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="progressive-disclosure" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Progressive Disclosure</name>

      <t>To support efficient consumption across different contexts,
      implementations SHOULD support progressive disclosure at four
      standard levels:</t>

      <dl>
        <dt>L0 - Headline (~50 tokens):</dt>
        <dd>canonical_question + consensus_level + first agreed claim.
        Suitable for search result listings.</dd>

        <dt>L1 - Summary (~200 tokens):</dt>
        <dd>All agreed claims + disputed claim texts (without per-model
        positions).  Suitable for agent context injection.</dd>

        <dt>L2 - Full (~1,000 tokens):</dt>
        <dd>All L1 fields + synthesis + per-model positions + uncertain
        array + source references.  Suitable for article display.</dd>

        <dt>L3 - Complete (full deliberation):</dt>
        <dd>All round response texts + individual receipt signatures.
        Suitable for audit and verification.</dd>
      </dl>

      <t>An agent querying a KU corpus SHOULD read L0 for all
      candidates, L1 for top matches, and L2 or L3 only for the selected
      KU.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="alt-serialization" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Alternative Serialization</name>

      <t>The canonical representation is JSON.  However, many knowledge
      management tools operate on YAML frontmatter with markdown bodies.
      Implementations MAY represent a KU as YAML frontmatter followed by
      a markdown body.  The markdown body maps to the synthesis field
      (editorial, not canonical).  When converting between formats, the
      agreed and disputed arrays MUST preserve their full structure.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="security" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>Security Considerations</name>

      <t>Model Collusion: If all models share the same bias, consensus
      may be spurious.  Implementations SHOULD include at least one model
      from a different training lineage.</t>

      <t>Synthesis Bias: The synthesis field is NOT canonical.  The
      agreed, disputed, and uncertain arrays are authoritative.</t>

      <t>Receipt Replay: Verifiers MUST check that receipt_hash covers
      the claimed content by recomputing the chain construction.</t>

      <t>Key Compromise: Implementations SHOULD support key rotation
      and publish revocation lists.</t>

      <t>Prompt Injection: Source material is context, not instruction.
      The adversarial critique round surfaces injected
      inconsistencies.</t>

      <t>Freshness: Consumers SHOULD check lifecycle state before
      relying on KU content.</t>

      <t>Source Integrity: When sources are available, content_hash
      enables verification that the source has not changed.
      Implementations SHOULD flag KUs with source hash mismatches as
      stale.</t>

      <t>Confidence Decay: KUs about rapidly evolving domains (volatility
      "volatile") should be consumed with appropriate scepticism even
      within their freshness window.</t>
    </section>

    <section anchor="iana" numbered="true" toc="default">
      <name>IANA Considerations</name>
      <t>This document has no IANA actions.  A future revision may
      request registration of a media type
      "application/vnd.acta.knowledge-unit+json".</t>
    </section>
  </middle>

  <back>
    <references>
      <name>References</name>

      <references>
        <name>Normative References</name>

        <xi:include href="https://bib.ietf.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.2119.xml"/>
        <xi:include href="https://bib.ietf.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.8032.xml"/>
        <xi:include href="https://bib.ietf.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.8174.xml"/>
        <xi:include href="https://bib.ietf.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.8785.xml"/>

        <reference anchor="I-D.farley-acta-signed-receipts">
          <front>
            <title>Signed Receipts for AI Agent Actions</title>
            <author fullname="Tom Farley" initials="T." surname="Farley">
              <organization>Veritas Acta</organization>
            </author>
            <date year="2026"/>
          </front>
          <seriesInfo name="Internet-Draft" value="draft-farley-acta-signed-receipts-01"/>
        </reference>
      </references>

      <references>
        <name>Informative References</name>
        <xi:include href="https://bib.ietf.org/public/rfc/bibxml/reference.RFC.9497.xml"/>
      </references>
    </references>
  </back>
</rfc>
